Two years ago, I had to get my ear operated
on because of tinnitus.
As I was laying on the cold operating table… Completely
paralyzed with fear...
That dreadful ringing which has been tormenting
me for years grew louder and louder!  I
wanted to scream: “Doctor, doctor! For
the love of God, please don’t cut my ear
off!”  But no words were coming out of
my mouth.  With the corner of my eye, I
saw the sharp scalpel getting closer and closer
to my ear… I said “God, help me!”
and then everything turned pitch black.
When I finally came back to my senses… The
surgeons told me they had to slice the back
of my ear and lay it wide open in order to
“fix” what they thought was wrong with
my horrible ear ringing.
“Well, we did open up your ear canal a bit
but the bones were intact,” the doctor said.
“Hopefully it still helps the severe tinnitus,
but we can’t be sure.”
Even so, days after the operation, my ears
were still ringing louder than ever… I
was completely devastated and I felt like
I would be stuck with Tinnitus FOREVER…
What happened to me, sooner or later can happen
to anyone… But even though that was the
most terrifying experience from my entire
life…
It was that precise nightmarish moment that
sent me on a mind-bending journey... Which
eventually led me to the discovery of a completely
natural and inexpensive method that makes
it possible for you to finally clear your
ringing and regain your hearing again!     Hi,
I’m Gerard Watson, and today I want to literally
bring truth to your ears…
That’s because in just a few moments, I’ll
show you where tinnitus REALLY comes from…
And how a simple technique recently discovered
by scientists at leading medical universities…
Could make it possible for you to hit the
“mute” button on that aggravating ringing
on your ears.
Scientists say that once you listen to a short
series of sound therapies and add a group
of certain natural ingredients in your diet…
you could re-train your brain to cut off the
ringing, roaring and whooshing in your ears…
That no matter how much earwax you dig out…
how many antibiotics your doctor gives you…
or how religiously you attempt to quiet the
noise banging around in your brain...
You’ll NEVER get rid of the debilitating
effects of tinnitus until it’s COMPLETELY
snuffed out.
And that’s really GOOD news… Because inside
this short presentation…
You’ll discover a totally natural technique
that could PULL THE PLUG on tinnitus, even
while you sleep.
Developed by a team of ear specialists and
sound technology experts… this technique
doesn’t require hearing aids, new chemical-laden
medications… chronic ear flushing, or surgery.
In fact, once you see exactly what this sound
therapy technique does… how it turns your
world so quiet and clear again…
You’ll be AMAZED at how SIMPLE and inexpensive
it is…
No more stuffing your head in the pillows
at night to escape the sounds roaring in your
ears…
Or dosing up on nighttime sleep meds just
to get a short reprieve…
Forget the headaches, dizziness and pure frustration
at being “trapped” in your own head, too…
It sounds incredible, I know…
But, as you’ll soon see with this brief
presentation…
Just by following a couple of easy techniques
that I’m about to show you…
You could enjoy the moments of silence you
longed for…
Bringing you INTENSE relief and the ability
to CONCENTRATE for once without having ear-piercing
sounds keeping you distracted…
And excelling at work without having to stop
and say: “What?” all the time.
You could be finally able to relax and enjoy
your family and friends, even in the noisiest
of environments.
Best of all, this strategic and scientific
technique is fit for ANYONE… no matter how
bad they suffer from tinnitus or how old they
are…
Because just by following the simple sound
therapy technique I’m about to show you…
Which, unlike everything else out there, is
even more powerful, as it is coupled with
a miraculous natural solution specifically
designed to calm down your nervous system,
not by a money hungry Big Pharma company,
but by a brave group of people who have been
struggling themselves with tinnitus for years...
Your brain could be re-trained to suffocate
tinnitus on a biological level…
Ridding your body of the anxiety resulting
from a never-ending noise explosion inside
your head…
Dramatically helping additional hearing problems
associated with tinnitus… cutting out the
possibility of major ear surgery…
And feeling like a “normal” person again.
Now, if you’ve suffered from tinnitus for
ANY length of time, I’m sure you’re curious
to find out this simple technique…
And take control of WHAT you hear and WHEN.
So let’s not waste any time…
I want you to know who I am…
Why I know a secret trick that ear…
And how you can put this secret to work for
YOU… in order to FINALLY achieve the blessed
peace of silence inside your head…
Even if you can’t remember how GOOD it actually
feels.
So, as you know, my name is Gerard Watson.
I’m 55 years old and live near Denver, Colorado…
And two years ago, doctors cut my ear off
my head to “fix” tinnitus.
The chief surgeon said the horrible hissing
sounds in my ears were the result of broken
ear bones, but after he cut into my head,
he discovered…
Nothing.
Nothing AT ALL was physically “wrong”
with my ears.
And I woke up feeling like he’d drilled
through my skull with an ice pick… My ear
was fire-hot and swollen off my head, stitched
back on like Frankenstein…
All for NOTHING.
The ringing in my ears not only remained there,
it got WAY more wicked after that…
And even worse, he’d accidentally cut a
facial nerve, so my tongue lost all taste
and felt like someone burned it with acid…
As you can imagine, this experience was horribly
eye opening…
Not to mention EXPENSIVE…
And I’ll tell you more about it in just
a couple seconds…
But before I do, it’s best if you know how
I got to the point of having my head cut open
to begin with…
Ever since I was a kid, I had bad ear infections
that kept my doctors dosing me with antibiotics.
I had tubes in my ears, poor hearing and learned
to read lips pretty early on…
I wasn’t deaf by ANY means, but ear problems
became the norm in my life from a young age,
even though nobody else in my family suffered
from it.
So, when my ears started ringing one day out
of the blue, I wasn’t too alarmed.
I mean, the older you get, the worse your
hearing becomes, right? The ringing and whooshing
in my head just became something I accepted…
Up until two years ago, when a drill siren
struck through my skull.
I was in a meeting with fellow music executives,
and all of a sudden, it was like someone banged
both sides of my head like a set of drums…
All I could hear was a high-pitch tone that
drowned everything else out… like that loud
alarm tone on the emergency broadcast system
when it takes over your TV...
I covered my ears and looked around at everyone
else…
But nobody was experiencing this weird pain…
they were all staring at me like I was crazy.
I left work early hoping it was just a fluke
and would go away…
But it didn’t.
The dinging stayed with me even into the night,
where it proceeded to keep me from sleeping
a wink.
The next day, it was still there… Only now,
there was a sensation of blood pumping through
my ears, too…
Concerned, I called around and asked a few
colleagues for the best ear specialist out
there…
After all, I was in the music industry, which
is notorious for causing hearing loss.
Luckily, I was able to get an appointment
right away, and the doctor…
Who was a top-notch surgeon who came HIGHLY
recommended…
Immediately sent me to get an MRI scan on
my head.
A few days later, as he reviewed the results
with me, the doctor said he still wasn’t
sure what was wrong with me.
“You do have unusually small ear canals,
which accounts for your infections growing
up,” he said. “And I do see a blockage
in your right ear, which could be a broken
bone, and that might make the tinnitus worse.”
“Okay,” I said. “So what now?”
My doctor said surgery was probably the safest
bet, and had my operation scheduled for the
next week.
It all happened so fast, and at the time I
was glad I’d be able to have the procedure
done so quickly.
Looking back however, I wish I’d known then
what I know now…
The surgeons had to slice the back of my ear
and lay it wide open in order to “fix”
what they thought was wrong.
Worse still, was the news my doctor gave me
when I finally got done throwing up from the
anesthesia…
“Well, we did open up your ear canal a bit
but the bones were intact,” he said. “Hopefully
it still helps the severe tinnitus, but we
can’t be sure.”
My ears were still ringing, a hot pulse surged
through my ear drums… I felt so utterly
deflated.
“One more thing,” he said. “We cut through
a taste nerve in your jaw. Your mouth might
tingle or burn for a little while, and have
a funny metal taste, but it will go away.
Happens quite often.”
So THAT was why my mouth felt halfway numb,
halfway on fire?! I thought it was the vomiting…
If this all sounds horribly disgusting, that’s
because it WAS.
Now I had tinnitus AND a severed taste nerve…
And I felt like I would be stuck with it all
FOREVER…
I was distracted all day at work, trying to
concentrate but getting thrown off by the
constant nagging in my eardrums…
They finally told me to take a leave of absence
because I couldn’t hear over the swooshing
sounds in my head, making me useless in the
music industry.
Not only was I anxiety-ridden and feeling
trapped inside my jail of a head… But I
was getting majorly depressed, too…
Which meant that no matter how I did it, I
needed to escape this life sentence of having
the nails dragged down the chalkboard in my
head… disturbing every part of my life.
And so from that moment on, every single moment
was spent researching medical publications,
studies, scientific journals and periodicals,
even alternative methods of treating tinnitus.
You have a lot of medical experts saying tinnitus
is almost impossible to treat with ANY method
because there isn’t one root cause for it…
They suspect loud noises or injuries to the
ears COULD lead to tinnitus, yet some people
suffer from it without ever being exposed
to damage.
Which makes sense because even though my doctors
told me I got it after years of listening
to music way too loudly…
I still knew a lot of people who suffered
from tinnitus their whole lives WITHOUT being
exposed to anything harmful to their hearing.
But even though they may not know exactly
what makes people get tinnitus, scientists
DO know what it does inside your head…
Tinnitus roots itself deep in the brain and
causes a complex interplay of brain signals
to go wrong. It begins with damage to tiny
vibrating receptors called “hair cells”
in the inner ear.
But regardless of why you get tinnitus or
what it does inside your brain, people are
still desperate for any possible remedy that
gets rid of it...
Like using hearing aids to “mask” the
sounds inside your head… expensive and annoying
to wear in your ears…
Anti-depression medication and “sleep”
drugs to calm the panic attacks and anxiety
kicked up by tinnitus… which don’t get
to the ROOT of the problem, just zone you
out…
Fake chemical remedies, acupuncture, meditation
are also used… Fine for overall calming
effect, but they cost a lot of money and are
not that effective.
And then there’s surgery, which I personally
knew doesn’t work… Let alone the physical
and financial pain…
As you can tell, the research was unnerving…
And I can’t tell you how many times I almost
gave up.
Well, there must be a higher power out there,
because barely a week later, I FINALLY found
the one thing that changed everything…
That would end up giving me peace of mind
back.
I’d searched the Internet, read piles of
books at the medical library and made a ton
of inquiries with doctors and specialists...
When I came across two obscure studies that
had me doing mental backflips.
Both of them came from an expensive site that
published medical journals for sound therapists
and research scientists, but the price meant
nothing if I could find the vital information
I was after.
The first study came from the Washington University
School of Medicine in St. Louis, and showed
tinnitus patients participating in computer-based
training reported incredible improvements.
Specifically, the study groups listened to
a series of sound recordings focused on improving
the processing of sound, speech and memory.
That sounded too good to be true, and it really
got my attention… Help your tinnitus by
doing the ONE thing you never thought you’d
normally do ever again—LISTENING.
And the second study came from the University
of San Francisco, where scientists had attempted
to use sound therapy to fix tinnitus…
Basically, the USF scientists were using a
customized acoustic “stimulus” delivery
system, called a “Neuromonics” device…
And it was introduced as a means of promoting
neural flexibility within the hearing system
in hopes of abolishing tinnitus-related ailments.
In plain English, what all this means is that
the researchers were playing a pattern of
audio stimuli…
Sounds that had been scientifically designed
to retrain your brain to get it working properly…
Well, after reading about these successes
with sound therapy techniques, I was completely
intrigued…
I mean, this was my background, I’d spent
my LIFE burning new sounds onto CDs… perhaps
I could do the same inside the human brain?
I began making calls to the smartest sound
technologists in the industry. Maybe someone
else knew about this, too.
Well, not long after I’d left messages for
every single composer, sound tech, music executive
and studio producer I knew… I had my breakthrough.
One of the major symphony composers of ALL
time returned my call.
He told me he’d suffered from hearing loss
and tinnitus for YEARS… but that he’d
overcome all of it by simply LISTENING to
a certain mix of altered music and audio tones.
He said he knew all about Neuromonics, which
required a special listening device and costs
$5000 for treatment…
“But it’s unnecessary, because with the
state-of-the-art equipment at the studio,
I created the same sounds at a fraction of
the cost.”
This guy was the BEST in the business, who’d
suffered from a case of tinnitus almost as
bad as mine before using his own version of
Neuromonics.
And it made sense, because top composers like
him are “doctors” of sound. They’re
mathematical geniuses and brilliant at knowing
exactly how music and tone works inside the
human brain.
So, I was definitely sold… And, even better,
he was willing to reproduce copies of his
recordings for me...
Now a REAL solution was within reach… and
it could help so many other people out there
suffering from the mildest forms of tinnitus
to the most severe cases…
You can’t imagine how relieved I was and
how anxious to get it working…
This was what I’d been searching for…
And when a huge box of hard drives arrived,
filled with the highest quality sound therapy
recordings, I stayed up all night sorting
through them.
In the end, I combined the two most effective
ways that could make your brain cut off tinnitus
and re-train itself naturally…
First, a version of Neuromonics that used
music, with soundtracks adjusted to scientific
algorithms that could provide a relief from
tinnitus…
There was also a ‘neural stimulus’ added
to these recordings to further aid the relaxation
response… a portion of which is purely used
while you sleep.
Second, I used sound therapy recordings based
on cognitive-behavioral instruction…
Put simply, these are brief listening exercises
focused on auditory speed, sound and memory
designed to improve brain functioning.
Once I had the 2-step sound therapy technique
sorted out, I grabbed my headphones to be
sure all of the recordings played back perfectly…
If this helped tinnitus sufferers, it would
be a miracle… especially because it was
so simple…
Something you only needed to listen to twice
a week, for 15-30 minutes…
Something anyone could do, regardless of their
severity of suffering…
And something that wouldn’t require any
costly doctor appointments or dangerous prescriptions.
I put the final touches on the sound techniques…
and dedicated the next 30 days to testing
the whole thing out.
First, I gathered a list of 20 people I knew
who suffered from various levels of tinnitus—myself
included—and asked them to test out the
sound therapy program.
Every single person accepted immediately.
Especially because we’d recorded the techniques
in such a way that no one needed to leave
their house or even buy special headphones
to listen …
They each received a weekly report form to
follow their progress and record listening
times.
I prepared to wait weeks for the initial reports
to come back.
But what happened next was amazing.
Even after one or two “hearing” sessions,
I was getting calls from everyone in the study,
claiming their tinnitus was WAY less intense.
They couldn’t believe it… And so I encouraged
them to stick with the listening sessions
and continue charting their progress.
Being one of the people who suffered the worst
from tinnitus, I had doubled up on my listening
to heighten the experiment…
Which still only put me at about 10 minutes
per day…
And so I was even more SHOCKED at how quickly
my ears started clearing up.
Soon enough, for at least 2 or 3 days in a
row, the horrible ringing was almost unnoticeable
and my depression was quickly lifting.
My headaches went away and I was sleeping
through the night without ANY problems.
And by week 4, most of my tinnitus symptoms
had disappeared. On a scale of 1 to 10,
my symptoms dilated down to a 3.  I was
not 100% treated, but it was way better than
anything else I have tried before.
But it wasn’t just me…
When I went to collect the reports from the
other subjects in my initial study…
The results I saw were astounding, with more
than half of the subjects reporting that
their tinnitus symptoms reduced by over 60%.
They also mentioned a significant improvement
in their hearing as well, which was an added
bonus I hadn’t foreseen.
This was the best news EVER…
I’d used my sound technology background
and trusted professionals in the music field
to find a solution.  Not a perfect one,
but something that I knew I can make even
better, so that everyone would finally be
100% tinnitus-free.
So, I returned to work with more mental clarity
and focus than ever…
You see… even though I knew for a fact
that listening to the special recordings will
definitely help silence that dreadful ringing
in the ears…
Just the sound therapy wouldn’t be enough. The
sound therapy indeed retrains the brain.  But
the brain still needs the proper nutrients
to heal and recover.
I mean - if you had tinnitus for more than
6 months of 1 year, there was still a lot
of brain and hair cells damage that was left
untreated, as you would imagine… If I
were to create 100% working tinnitus treatment,
I definitely could not neglect undoing the
brain damage. Otherwise, just using the
sound therapy would be like a band aid - fixing
the problems only in the short term and not
actually addressing the root cause of the
problem.   So, my next questions were
how could I undo all the brain damage caused
by tinnitus and what was the most effective
way to calm down the nervous system and bulletproof
anyone against any future tinnitus comeback?
So here’s what I did: I created
an on-line tinnitus sufferers group, which
grew to at least a couple of thousands people
in just a matter of weeks.
It was like our little family - where everyone
was encouraged to share their experiences
and what natural solutions seemed to work
best in the long fight against tinnitus.  You
see, I thought if we combined all our powers,
we will definitely find a working treatment
for this…
Something we would all know that would work…
Something tried and tested by us - the tinnitus
sufferers - not by a faceless, money-grubbing
pharmaceutical company...
And I must admit - I’m not a big believer
in God, but there sure is a higher power out
there, because barely 3 weeks later, I FINALLY
found the one thing that changed everything…
As one German hearing specialist from our
on-line group pointed me to a recent little-known
study from the German Research Foundation. You
see, according to this study, there was a
neuron-soothing natural component that quiets
the roaring-brain cells in your head called
Diosgenin, which can be naturally extracted
from yam or fenugreek, among other plants.
Well, I must admit - I’ve never heard of
Diosgenin before.  But when I began to further
investigate this, I found out that this substance
was also being used with extraordinary success
in Japan as well.
You see - the Japanese researchers took
28 otherwise healthy Tinnitus volunteers from
the Toyama Prefecture, in Japan, and they
randomly assigned who will receive either
a yam extract or placebo.
After 12 weeks on the Diosgenin treatment,
the volunteers were given 12 individual standard
cognitive subtests…
The results awed the researchers!
Diosgenin-rich yam extract use significantly
improved their brain performance while shifting
the attention of the overactive brain cells
to other areas of the brain.
Memory, cognition, hearing, attention, relaxation…
Everything skyrocketed while the sound that
tormented their ears was basically shut off!
This was absolutely incredible!    Moreover,
after analyzing all the responses pouring
in from the thousands of tinnitus sufferers
in the on-line group, a number of herbs, plants
and minerals stood up, which everybody claimed
worked wonders when things got really bad
with their tinnitus.   I knew then for
a fact that compiling the right mix of all
these natural ingredients would be the ultimate
weapon against Tinnitus.
After all, they were proven to work not just
by one person, but by thousands of folks of
all ages from all across the word!
I’m sure that you’re curious to find out
what this natural anti-tinnitus mix is and
why does it work so incredibly well?
So please, pay careful attention now, because
the following information comes from our private
medical research, to which the general public
has no access to:
Here's a short, step-by-step explanation of
each one of the anti-tinnitus brain repairing
ingredients used and how they work...
After intensive lab testing, they have proven
to be 100% effective ONLY in this formula,
specifically calculated and adjusted to give
the best possible results against tinnitus
and brain disorders...
STEP 1: Your hearing begins to clear as the
brain networks and your inner ear “hair
cells” are getting repaired, cooling down
the nervous system.
So your tinnitus is driving you crazy and
you can’t stand it for another moment. Both
German and Japanese scientists have chosen
Yam and Fenugreek as the “first aid duo”
that can lower the sound from the very first
days, thanks to their high levels of Diosgenin.
This happens because this emergency team quickly
repairs the buzzing brain networks. Also,
the yam “cools down” the entire nervous
system, while Fenugreek prevents panic attacks.
There are over 600 species of yam, but during
our research we’ve found that Mexican Wild
Yam has the most effective type of Diosgenin.
STEP 2: You regain your quiet mind while your
brain networks are strengthening and becoming
indestructible.
Dong Quai, a super-herb not many know about,
may take a little longer to kick in but it’s
the one ingredient that definitely puts a
run to tinnitus while helping your brain networks
to become stronger than steel.
Not only that but, as shown during multiple
lab tests, Dong Quai also acts like a merciless,
double guardian. A guardian of the brain-
protecting it against potentially fatal problems
- and a guardian of the ears – protecting
them against infections. Saw Palmetto, on
the other hand - balances your hormone levels
- thus preventing irreversible cells damage
while also decreasing brain and inner ear
inflammation
STEP 3: You feel your memory is stronger than
ever while your damaged brain cells are quickly
being repaired.
L-Tyrosine, an essential amino-acid found
in certain types of cheese, is vital for
your brain, as it produces important brain
chemicals that help nerve cells communicate
better and may even regulate mood.
Now, because your brain networks were “broken”by
tinnitus, your brain cells didn’t connect
properly, which resulted in multiple damages,
dramatically increasing a risk in loss of
memory…
But the right dosage of high quality L-Tyrosine
does the impossible by repairing YEARS of
brain deterioration…
As researchers discovered, after just a short
10-day L-Tyrosine treatment, patients with
severe cases of memory loss began regaining
their memories and showed significant improvements
in their thinking and behaviour.
Adding Fennel, which is packed with important
nutrients such as Vitamin C, Calcium, Magnesium
and Potassium, will powers up your memory
and fight off dementia.
This is also the phase when you say goodbye
to fatigue, sleepless nights, dizziness and
brain fog.
STEP 4: You feel your brain is supercharged
while cell regenerations starts.
This is when your mind begins to get super
powers.
Motherwort, Black Cohosh and Oat Grass are
like steroids for the brain. As you age, your
brain gets smaller. But not with these three
ingredients as they grow your brain, fire
up connections and help cell rejuvenation.
The “tinnitus” brain can become more than
10 years younger and you’ll think faster,
better, clearer.
STEP 5: Not worrying about tinnitus and brain
disorders anymore because your brain is being
trained for perfect health.
Finally, this one-of-a-kind formula protects
the brain against tinnitus, memory loss or
other debilitating conditions by combining
high quality Pacific Kelp, Blessed Thistle
and Hops Extract. While the Pacific Kelp
and Blessed Thistle are full of antioxidants
and anti-inflamatory, thus cleaning your brain
of toxins, the Hops Extract helps to multiply
the neural connections, improving your brain
function and mood, relieving stress, anxiety
and depression.
The “old age” rule, where your mind and
memory start to decline, will be so far from
you from this point forward.
There you have it: the ultimate tinnitus terminator
natural mix,  All we had to do now was to
make it available for everybody: we had dozens
of doctors to provide the medical knowledge
and a state of the art lab all to ourselves.
The most difficult part was to gather all
the ingredients.
You see, the market is full of counterfeit,
cheap knock-offs of so-called "natural homeopathic
ingredients".
We know this because, after we've carefully
tested 97% of the available natural Mexican
Wild Yam extracts, Blessed Thistle or Black
Cohosh leaves... we found out they were bogus
and derived from chemicals, and not from natural
sources.
So we searched the whole world through our
scientific connections and contacted only
certified producers and verified suppliers,
making sure that for our recipe we used only
top quality ingredients, with 100% healing
properties.
It was very difficult and exhausting...
We secretly worked night after night, testing
until dawn, making sure that we got the right
quantities and the most effective combination
of ingredients….
And there were times when I was so tired that
I even threw up, but in the end, there it
was!
My hands were shaking as I was finally holding
the pills that would undo all the tinnitus
brain damage and bring my life and dignity
back!
If this tiny, natural pill, combined with
the sound therapy, was the effective treatment
to tinnitus, it would be a miracle, especially
because it was so simple.
Anyone could take it, regardless of their
severity of suffering;
It didn’t require any costly doctor appointments
or trying any other therapies;
It protected you from the most frightening
brain disorders like amnesia or memory loss..
Of course, I was the very first one who tried
it.
After the first pill, I didn’t feel a thing.
Well, maybe hope, which, was still something
I thought that I’d lost forever!
But soon after, everything completely changed:
I was even more SHOCKED at how quickly
my head and ears started clearing up.
Not only that, but my brain fog went away
and I was sleeping through the night without
ANY problems…
So even though my tinnitus was gone thanks
to the sound therapy, I kept taking the pills,
just to see what would happen…
And sooner than I thought, the results began
to appear:  It was like I had a brand new
brain!
My mind was sharp, I could focus easily and
my memory was crystal clear.
Also, my old migraines had disappeared completely...
And it wasn't just me...
When I went to collect the reports from the
other subjects in my initial study...
The results I saw were astounding!
Not a single person reported getting the high-pitched
OR low-pitched ringing in their ears anymore...
Or hearing their heart beat all day...
And they also reported a HUGE reduction in
hearing loss too, which was an added bonus
I hadn't foreseen…
Judging by my own miraculous results, I had
anticipated most of these successes...
But when I heard that one of the participants
in our study had his early onset memory loss
diagnosis treated…I knew I had a mission…
I couldn’t keep this life-saving treatment
all to myself…
We decided to combine the sound therapy program
together with the brain recovery solution
and make it available for everybody who's
tormented by tinnitus.
This is how the “Neurocalm Protocol” was
born!
A revolutionary 2 step program to terminate
tinnitus once and for all:
First, the sound therapy techniques inside
this program will “unplug” your brain
from its internal loud speakers just by LISTENING...
simply and with no effort on your part.
So I gathered the piles of research and recordings
we’d worked on… And began laying out the
techniques in a simple and easy format for
ANYONE who might want to use them…
Then I created an initial evaluation questionnaire
for tinnitus, to gauge severity for individual
recommendations on which sound recordings
work best…
I categorized all of the sound therapy sessions
based on what part of the brain they worked
on, and gave technical breakdowns for how
the sounds were altered or enhanced for maximum
potency…
I formatted “listening session” charts
and times, detailing the 30-day program tested
on the study group… Including the weekly
report forms for tracking your success…
And lastly, I outlined a general FAQ list
for tinnitus and how it disrupts the ear canals,
as well as known causes for the disease, suspected
culprits… plus a general “how-to”
section to help you protect your hearing.
The second part of the protocol is based
on the Neurocalm Pro supplement, which is
absolutely crucial and will repair your brain
networks damaged by tinnitus and calm down
your nervous system.  This unique mix of
natural ingredients can without a doubt be
called “the ultimate weapon against Tinnitus.”
After all, all the ingredients inside were
proven to work not just by one person, but
by thousands of tinnitus sufferers of all
ages from all across the word! Moreover,
it was fully backed by science as well - as
both German and Japanese researchers showed
without a doubt that Diosgenin can effectively
“shut off” ear ringing and improve brain
performance, memory, attention and even hearing!
Now that you know the entire story...
You're probably asking two questions:
How can I get my hands on this amazing program?
How should I use this protocol to get the
fastest results and get my silence back?
Well, to answer question one is a little bit
tricky....  Even though getting the sound
therapy program is pretty easy - actually
- you can even start using it in the next
5 minutes…
When it comes to the wonder-supplement Neurocalm
Pro, things change a bit...
You see.. the truth is that getting the right
ingredients to make this powerful anti-tinnitus
pill is difficult.
As I said, 97% of the "natural" ingredients
on the market are either fake, or filled with
pesticides.
Also, the people who have already tested our
product and regained their long, lost silence
keep asking us for more bottles for themselves,
for their families and friends...
Or just to stock up in case we won't be able
to provide anymore and to make sure that they
will have the power to fight tinnitus for
the rest of their lives.
Plus, there are folks who don’t have tinnitus,
but just take the supplement to rejuvenate
their brain…
Emptying our stocks in just a matter of days.
Moreover, Neurocalm Pro is carefully produced
only in small batches that take up to 3 months
to deliver…
This process is essential to assure that the
quality of the product is 100% effective!
And don't forget about Big Pharma who are
already hunting us like mad for ruining their
profits that come from innocent people who
are desperate to get a minute of relief.
But since you’ve stuck with me until the
very end of my story, in the next few minutes,
you'll find out how to get your hands on a
brand-new bottle of supplements, as part of
our awareness campaign.  As for how you
should use this protocol to get the fastest
results and get my silence back, the answer
is easy:
All you have to do is take 2 pills on a
daily basis for at least 30 days and listen
to the sound therapy recordings twice a week
for 15 minutes each time… It could NOT be
any simpler.
All the strategic tools and knowledge you’ll
ever need can be found within the program.
You’ll see the techniques that could “trick”
your brain into reprogramming itself and eliminating
that ringing in your ears…
Simply follow the instructions inside the
program, showing you how to use the recordings
to cut out the internal invasion of sound,
quiet your mind, promote relaxation and renew
your outlook on life.
There’s no doubt that f you follow the Neurocalm
Protocol, your mind will be quiet sooner than
y
in just a couple of weeks...
Then it’s up to you how far you want to
go.
Maybe you want to significantly decrease your
risk of memory disorders and feel how your
brain is being supercharged and regenerated...in
which case it could take at least 75 days
to treat the deterioration caused by the damaged
brain networks…which means 3 bottles of
Neurocalm Pro…
Or- and this is a popular choice among the
people who contact us- you want the best chances
against memory loss or other brain disorders,
while treating tinnitus… in which case 6
months and 6 bottles of Neurocalm Pro are
all you need..
We cannot estimate exactly how damaged your
brain networks are at this point.
This depends on many factors, such as how
old your tinnitus is, your medical history,
your overall state of health and lifestyle
choices etc.
So, as a rule of thumb, after seeing the positive
results of more than 47,000 people suffering
chronic tinnitus, we recommend to take at
the very least 3 bottles (6 bottles or more
to be completely safe), for a period of 90
days.
This should be enough to completely regenerate
your brain, supercharge and protect it against
tinnitus and memory disorders.
It’s a fact since many people have confirmed
the results with such dramatic success.
Like Jeremy Seaton, 45, Pennsylvania
I’ve always said I’d cut off at least
three of my fingers for a magic pill that
banishes tinnitus and I’m sure I’m not
the only one… Actually seeing this sound
therapy and pill exists, it feels like a miracle…
My head is quieter than EVER, and I can't
even remember a time my whole body felt this
calm.
My mind is clear, the brain fog is gone…it’s
like I’ve suddenly got this special brain
power. And this is just the second month since
I began taking the pills…I’m sharing this
with everyone I know, it’s the least I can
do.”
Sarah M., 58, Kentucky
I didn’t believe for a second in what you
were saying, Gerard. Just 15 minutes daily
of the sound therapy and 2 pills a day to
end years of chronic tinnitus and keep your
brain safe from memory disorders? Please,
go bark up another tree...
It was my daughter the one who insisted I
take them, we argued a lot. It’s true what
they say…children are smarter than their
parents.
I had ringing in my left ear and a pulsing
sensation in my right ear all the time before
I started this incredible protocol…all gone
now. I still can’t believe it.
It’s like a curse has been lifted. I feel
blessed and alive.
Val T., 60, Detroit
I was stuck with hearing aids to stifle the
sounds. I could barely go through life each
day. But after a couple weeks of this therapy
I threw them away.
My husband can't believe I understand everything
he says and can even answer questions from
another room.
My headaches are gone and even though I always
forgot where I put my keys, I don’t anymore.
I also remember birthdays. Used to fear
memory loss …not anymore.
I’m happy my husband began to take these
pills too. He doesn’t have tinnitus, he
takes them for his brain. Everybody should.
I’m never giving them up.
People are getting their lives and peace of
mind back as we speak…
Using a completely natural and side effect
free revolutionary protocol…
And all it takes to quiet your mind is 15
minutes of your time and 2 pills a day.
So, knowing all of this, it's obvious why
the Neurocalm Protocol dominates any other
option to successfully treat tinnitus... Nothing
else out there proved to WORK...
You could go to a doctor, who will torture
you with tons of useless tests or quickly
prescribe you expensive medicine that cause
dizziness, stomach problems and fatigue…
Medicine unproven to stop tinnitus because
it's not a bacterial infection or virus, but
a disease of the networks that connect the
brain...
Or maybe he'll talk you into an expensive
hearing aid to "cover up" the constant sound
waves exploding in your head...
Annoying and embarrassing to wear-and good
luck getting your insurance to cover the cost!
Next, your doctor might try prescribing depression
meds and sleeping pills to deafen the depression
and anxiety caused by tinnitus... but those
methods can't get to the root of the problem,
they're just addictive chemicals that turn
you into a zombie and prevent you from feeling
and experiencing life to its fullest.
There are alternative remedies like fake herbal
extracts and acupuncture, even meditation
to calm down the extreme stress tinnitus causes...
Which maybe doesn't hurt but surely is NOT
strong enough to be that treat-all you're
wishing for.
And then there’s sound therapy that is barely
worth mentioning.
All of these are a waste of time, energy and
money and you know it.
They won’t get you well in a million years…
Unlike the Neurocalm Protocol that can get
the job done in just a couple of weeks while
keeping you safe from future brain disorders…
You can understand why I initially wanted
to set the value for one bottle of Neurocalm
Pro and the entire Neurocalm Protocol at $99.
And, if you see this from my point of view,
I’m sure you can understand why.
I mean, once you go through the program—the
sound therapy recordings, 30-day kick start
kit, personalized progress charts, tinnitus
FAQ lists…
You could rebalance your brain to handle sounds
correctly… Shut down the ringing, roaring,
whooshing and blood pumping… Stop the headaches
and sleepless nights…
And if you pair this up with the unique Neurocalm
Pro supplement, you could rapidly restore
mental health as your mind quiets down and
adjusts to the real world of sound going on
around you…
Which, trust me, is beautiful… not painful
or irritating, like it seems now.
Also, all the ingredients inside Neurocalm
Pro are natural, some of them quite rare and
hard to obtain...
Plus, this special formula is designed for
the root cause of tinnitus, which is a life-threatening
disease of your brain networks, one that could
eventually lead you to severe memory loss
and even dementia.
Also, add on the costs of seeing a specialist
in your area, including the diagnoses he’ll
make you pay for and the drugs he is going
to prescribe to you…
Well, given all of this, $99 should seem like
a TOTAL STEAL.
But like I mentioned already, the Neurocalm
Protocol is not about us making a profit.
Sure, it would be nice to get paid for our
work and efforts but if we wanted money, we
could accept Big Pharma’s proposal right
now, close this page and get ourselves a bank
account ten times fatter than a Jackpot winner’s.
But we don't want their filthy money. All
we want is to help you and people like you
get truly better. That’s what my story and
mission meant from the start.
I wish this miraculous sound therapy and miraculous
pills protocol existed before the doctors
cut my ear off my had to “fix” my tinnitus,
traumatizing me for life…
But the past can’t be changed and what
matters now is that, after receiving emails
from people who can't afford the Neurocalm
Protocol, we knew we had to find a way so
EVERYONE could afford it…
Which is why there’s no chance I could consider
charging you $99 for this.
And because you’re watching this presentation,
you will benefit from a discount for Neurocalm
Pro from our awareness campaign...
If you act today, through this website...
and make the life changing decision of investing
in this extraordinary anti-tinnitus weapon...
You can get the only effective treatment that
allowed thousands of people to finally hit
the mute button on tinnitus...
For only $69
But you know what?
I'm going to make the deal even sweeter.
Because I know how hard it is to live paralyzed
by that hellish sound day after day, and night
after night…
I want people to have what I now have… And
I want to get this program out to as many
people as possible in order to accomplish
that… So I’m not bothering with profits.
That’s why I've set up a discounted package
system of 6 bottles of Neurocalm Pro and the
sound therapy protocol for you, for only $49
dollars, for a total of $294 which is being
offered TODAY ONLY... for as long as supplies
last. You also get free shipping on us.
But because this unique protocol works best
only together with Neurocalm Pro, once we
run out of bottles, the "BUY NOW" buttons
will not be active anymore until we make another
batch again (which takes around 2-3 months
at least).
Click the 6-bottle package (or any other package
that you want) below to secure your order.
Consider this the smallest, but most powerful
investment that you have ever made for yourself!
Yes, the sound therapy program and 1 bottle
of Neurocalm Pro might shut down the ringing,
roaring, whooshing and blood pumping sounds…
3 bottles might be enough to rapidly restore
your mental health, help with brain cells
rejuvenation by 15 years or more while getting
you rid of migraines, insomnia and brain shrinkage…
But 6 bottles of Neurocalm Pro and the unique
sound therapy program could make your brain
immune not only to tinnitus, but to memory
loss, amnesia and dementia …just imagine
being independent and free from old age problems!
You could turn 102- years old and your mind
would still be sharp as a tack!
You may be saying,
“OK, this sounds amazing and I'm interested!
How do I get started?”
Click the yellow button below after choosing
the best package for you, and you'll end up
on our secure checkout page. Enter your payment
details, place the order... and in 7 days
from this moment, you'll get Neurocalm Pro
delivered to your home!
Also, you'll gain immediate access to the
entire Neurocalm Sound Therapy Protocol, the
30-Day Kick-start program, the “listening
session” charts and the sound therapy sessions
- which can be accessed right away from your
computer, iPad or smartphone.  You can print,
download and listen to anything you want,
whenever you like.
BUT CLICK NOW, IT’S THE ONLY WAY SECURE
YOUR PACKAGE WHILE SUPPLIES LAST!
You have absolutely nothing to risk because
you are
also covered by our
60 Days "100% Healthy Or Money Back" Guarantee.
You can access the program immediately and
kickstart your journey towards a normal life
after just one listening session… You
can trust in what the sound technologists
and scientific researchers have discovered…
That your brain can be swiftly re-trained
to operate its inner sound system NORMALLY
again… That this sound therapy program is
the ONLY internal dial that turns tinnitus
ALL the way down.
And if you pair this with the ground-breaking
Neurocalm Pro, you can see for yourself how
your ringing becomes less and less intense
until it eventually vanishes... how your anxiety
and panic attacks fade away... and how you
are finally surrounded by silence again..
Just like our more than 47,000 satisfied customers
found out.
If you're unsatisfied for any reason (it's
rare but just in case) send us an email in
the Members' area, and you'll get a prompt
refund, no questions asked.
We'll still be friends.
You have nothing to risk at all. Like I said,
this is a 100% risk-free investment. So click
one of the buttons below to get started on
your journey of becoming tinnitus free.
But please, know you really do have to act
now. We are offering the Neurocalm Protocol
for just $69, and even cheaper if you are
getting our more popular packages, just to
get this amazing program into more hands.
But we are planning on raising the price back
to $99, or possibly much higher in the future.
Because here's the weird thing. When I tell
people that you can easily fight tinnitus
and from brain disorders…in practically
no time and for less than a visit to a specialist...
well, most people think it’s unbelievable,
as if there's something "fishy" going on.
It just sounds too cheap, especially if you
have been struggling to cure it with your
doctor's prescriptions or with who knows what
other methods…
Our mission is to spread the Neurocalm Protocol
to as many people as humanly possible, and
the big dream is for tinnitus and brain disorders
to be a thing of the past!
But if people find it hard to believe that
you can get such incredible results for less
than the cost of a visit to a specialist,
or a meal with your family at a restaurant,
then we'll have to raise the price.
Not to mention we don’t know how much longer
we’ll be able to hide from Big Pharma’s
threats.
But if this website is still up, it means
you can still get Neurocalm Protocol if you
act now.
Click to make your choice below, enter your
payment details, and place the order now.
Neurocalm Pro will arrive at your doorstep
in a matter of days. Also, you'll gain immediate
access to the entire Neurocalm Protocol, the
30-Day Kick-start program, the “listening
session” charts and the sound therapy sessions
- which can be accessed right away from your
computer, iPad or smartphone.  You can print,
download and listen to anything you want,
whenever you like.
Listen, when you think about it, you really
only have two choices ahead of you right now.
Option one: Stop following this presentation
and leave this page. Do nothing. Keep going
the way you are now, with that crucifying
sound following you everywhere and risking
serious brain conditions.
Keep being frustrated that nothing works,
spend hundreds, maybe thousands of dollars
on useless therapies, live with your tinnitus
for the following months... maybe even years,
or decades. It's not going to be pleasant.
Option two: Risk nothing at all today. Grab
Neurocalm Protocol right now. And you'll be
surprised at how well it works.
So just click below to make your choice, enter
your payment details, and place the order
now. You’ll get instant access to the entire
sound therapy program and we'll immediately
ship your bottles directly to your home.
I hope to hear your success story soon!
STILL HERE?
That's fine, this presentation covered so
much information that you might have some
questions.
So I’ll just take a moment to answer a few
questions that are usually asked by clients
before choosing the Neurocalm Protocol...
Question 1: How does the Neurocalm Protocol
work? Can you explain it again?
The Neurocalm Protocol is a revolutionary
2 step program to terminate tinnitus once
and for all:
First, the sound therapy techniques inside
this program will “unplug” your brain
from its internal loud speakers just by LISTENING...
simply and with no effort on your part.  Secondly,
the Neurocalm Pro supplement, which is absolutely
crucial to repair your brain networks damaged
by tinnitus and calm down your nervous system.
3. What am I getting inside the Neurocalm
Sound therapy protocol?
The techniques inside this program are represented
in a simple and easy format for anyone who
might want to use them. You’ll fill out
an initial evaluation questionnaire for tinnitus
to gauge severity for an individual recommendation
on which sound recordings work best.
In the 30-Day kick-start program, you’ll
receive “listening session” charts and
times, including weekly report forms for tracking
your progress. You’ll get a categorized
list of all the sound therapy sessions based
on what part of the brain they work on, with
technical breakdowns for how the sounds have
been altered or enhanced for maximum potency.
Lastly, you’ll receive a general FAQ list
for tinnitus and how it disrupts the ear canals,
as well as known causes for the disease and
suspected culprits… plus a general “How
To” section to help you protect your hearing.
Combined altogether, the techniques inside
this program “unplug” your brain from
its internal loud speakers just by listening—simply
and with no effort on your part.
4. How does the Neurocalm Pro supplement
work ?
Scientists discovered that tinnitus goes way
beyond than just the annoying, non-stop ear-ringing.
In fact, tinnitus is just a signal of brain
networks getting destroyed.
Unfortunately, memory loss, dementia and so
many other memory disorders start with the
failure of brain networks. To put it simply:
Your brain is a ticking time-bomb and tinnitus
is the emergency alert.
Now, the supplement works in the following
way:
STEP 1: Your hearing begins to clear as the
brain networks are getting repaired and the
nervous system calmed down.
The “buzzing” brain networks are quickly
fixed and the intensity of tinnitus sounds
being to lower in the first few days.
STEP 2: You regain your quiet mind while your
brain networks are strengthening and becoming
indestructible.
Tinnitus is attacked out by the incredibly
strong brain connections.
STEP 3: You feel your memory stronger than
ever while your damaged brain cells are quickly
being repaired.
Wiping out years of brain deterioration resulted
from the “broken” networks.
STEP 4: You feel your brain supercharged while
cell regenerations begins.
The “tinnitus” brain that made you a vegetable
is now being rejuvenated: you think faster,
better, clearer. It’s like your brain is
on steroids.
STEP 5: Not worrying anymore about tinnitus
and brain disorders because your brain is
being trained for a perfect health.
Your brain is being cleaned of toxins and
plaque, your neural connections are multiplying,
while a shield against tinnitus and memory
loss is being created.
Question 2: Can I take Neurocalm Pro even
if I have allergies or if I currently use
other supplements?
We created this amazing anti-tinnitus weapon
so that it has no damaging effect on people
who have various allergies, as the quantities
of the ingredients inside are selected to
be below the allergy-triggering levels.
But we recommend that, if you have any known
allergies to one of the mentioned pill ingredients,
you do not take this supplement.
For more details, please check the Disclaimer
link at the bottom of this page.
Question 3: Why haven't I heard of this protocol
before?
Well, as I explained during the presentation,
tinnitus and memory loss drug industry is
a $25 billion- a-year industry business.
But what the general public is unaware of
is that the drug industry literally spends
millions and millions of dollars each year
to ensure that academic medicine focuses only
on the drugs that make industry money, and
not on the drugs that will actually help people
get better.
Question 4: Is this program for everyone?
Yes! It could work successfully and safely
for people of any age. The sound therapy techniques
are non-invasive, relaxing and retrain your
brain to quickly and effortlessly silence
tinnitus—giving your ears and mind the relief
to achieve anything you want while feeling
amazing in the process. At the same time
Neurocalm Pro is safe for people of any age,
non-invasive and risk-free. It works by helping
your damaged brain networks to quickly and
effortlessly fight tinnitus, giving your mind
the relief to achieve anything you want while
feeling amazing in the process.
This program has also proved to be successful
for people with early onset of memory loss.
This is not unusual, since Neurocalm Pro was
designed to also rejuvenate brain cells. As
I told you before, tinnitus is just an emergency
alert that announces something’s wrong deep
inside in your brain. Dealing with the root
cause of tinnitus means dealing with any existing
brain damage.
Question 5: What happens once I click one
of the options below?
Once you click one of the options below, you'll
go to our 100% secure checkout page. You just
enter your payment information, and place
the order.
You’ll get instant access to every part
of the Neurocalm Protocol sound therapy, which
you can download, listen to and even print
as many times as you need.  As for the Neurocalm
Pro - we'll immediately ship your supplement
straight to your home, which should arrive
in just a couple of days.
It's that easy.
Question 6: How long does it really take
to see results?
As I've told you, and I'm very proud to repeat
this, you'll see the results amazingly fast.
As soon as you begin the sound therapy program,
the battle against tinnitus is half won! In
no time your tinnitus will become less and
less intense until it will eventually surrender
to silence. This, coupled with the Neurocalm
Pro supplement, will ensure that your brain
networks damage will be repaired and your
nervous system will calm down.
Question 7: What are the terms of that guarantee
that you've mentioned?
Because I want you to feel completely confident
in your investment today, I'm providing you
with a 60-day money back guarantee.
Simply click one of the buttons below, and
try the program out yourself for the next
60 days.
If you don't get the results I promised in
the shorterst amount of time possible... or
you're unsatisfied for any reason... simply
send an email to us in the Members' Area,
and I'll give you your money back. No questions
asked.
It should be clear that if I thought this
wasn't going to work, there's no way I would
make such an offer. But I do know this will
work... a total of more than 47,000 people
have already proven it.
Question 8: How long will this program be
available to the public?
Well, I'm not really sure, but history has
shown us that Big Pharma is not afraid to
spend millions of dollars in legal fees to
remove something that threatens its very existence.
If you think about it, that makes sense. Wouldn't
you spend 1 million dollars in lawyer costs
to protect the $25 billion per year you make?
In other words, if you are truly serious about
fighting your tinnitus and protecting your
brain against memory disorders in the following
days, you need to take action immediately.
Question 9: How do I get the Neurocalm Protocol?
This one is easy: Simply choose your package
by clicking on one of the options below, and
try out the entire program for yourself, for
60 days, with absolutely no risk. If you are
unhappy for any reason, you'll be given a
prompt refund, no questions asked...
That being said, I am supremely confident
you won't be asking for a refund because this
program has been proven to be effective for
anyone suffering from tinnitus... even if
they’ve had it for 10, or 20 years.
So click below. Fill in your payment details
and submit your order.
I can't wait to hear your success story!